<resources>

<string name="textoalan">Alan Mathison Turing OBE (Paddington, London, June 23, 1912 - Cheshire East, Cheshire, June 7, 1954) was a mathematician, logician, cryptanalyst and scientist of British computing. He was influenced by computer computation and the formalization of the algorithm concept and the computation with the Turing machine, playing an important role in the creation of the modern computer. [1] [2] [3] He was also a pioneer in artificial intelligence and computer science. [4] He is known as the father of computing.
During World War II, Turing worked for the British intelligence in Bletchley Park, in a center specialized in breaking of code. For a time he was head of Hut 8, a section responsible for the cryptanalysis of the German naval fleet. A number of techniques for German industries, including the electromechanical pump method, an electromechanical machine that can be found on an Enigma machine.
</string>

<string name="Jonv">John von Neumann, born Margittai Neumann János Lajos (Budapest, December 28, 1903 - Washington, D.C., February 8, 1957) was a Hungarian mathematician of Jewish origin, naturalized American.

He contributed to set theory, functional analysis, ergodic theory, quantum mechanics, computer science, economics, game theory, numerical analysis, hydrodynamics of explosions, statistics and many other areas of mathematics. In fact it is considered one of the most important mathematicians of century XX.

He was a member of the Princeton Institute of Advanced Studies, New Jersey, which also included Albert Einstein and Erwin Panofsky, when they emigrated to the United States, as well as Kurt Gödel, Robert Oppenheimer, George F. Kennan and Hermann Weyl. With Edward Teller and Stanisław Ulam, von Neumann worked on key developments in Nuclear Physics, related to thermonuclear reactions and the hydrogen bomb. He also participated in the Manhattan Project, responsible for the development of the first atomic bombs.

</string>
   
</resources>